Contact

Riverside, CA 714-392-5977 (Mobile) melissarbaskins@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ melissarenepeterson (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Quality Patient Care Patient Safety Interpersonal Skills

Certifications

Advanced Cardiovascular Life Support (ACLS)

NIHSS

EKG/Pharmacology Certification Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Honors-Awards

Dean's List

Dean's List

Dean's List

Dean's List

Dean's List

Melissa (Missy) Peterson

Bachelor of Science educated nurse actively seeking RN New Graduate Position

Greater Los Angeles Area

Summary

Compassionate Bachelor of Science educated nurse with special interest in Trauma. Strong academic background combined with over 16 years in customer service. Eagerly looking for an opportunity to utilize my skills within a RN New Graduate Program. Ideally, I would love to follow my passion and specialize in any critical care/Trauma setting. However, keeping an open mind if granted the opportunity to grow with a great company and transition into the specialty that I desire.

Experience

Right at Home, LLC. Home Health Aide August 2019 - February 2020 (7 months)

Rancho Cucagomona

Professionally provide in-home care for disabled, cognitively impaired, and chronically ill patients. Perform and assist with activities of daily living such as bathing, toileting, feeding, grooming, and dressing. Provide care with safe and confidential environments; Ensure safety with prevention of falls and accidents. Light chores, food preparation, and transportation to and from medical appointments. Assess patient and family needs. Ensure physiological, rehabilitative, and self-care needs. Documented and maintained thorough daily assessment patient logs.

-Achievements: Top trusted rapport with clients and families

The Boathouse on the Bay
Food Server
January 2011 - October 2018 (7 years 10 months)
Long Beach, California

State certified in food handling and safety. Versatility in rotating shifts and positions. Responsibilities as lead server, trainer, banquet server, with open and closing duties. Strong multitasking abilities, with effective performance under pressure while maintaining a friendly and professional demeanor.

Attentive to all specific requests and needs. Ensured optimal guest experience and developed genuine connections with regular customers.

- Achievements: Top positively reviewed server in annual Yelp contest.

Black Angus Steakhouse
Bartender and Server
January 2007 - January 2011 (4 years 1 month)
Fountain Valley, California, United States

Dual positions held as bartender, server, and cocktail server that delivered a consistently high level of customer service to each client. Maintained a safe environment and kept bar clean in accordance with company guidelines and local health department. Managed an accurate cash drawer throughout each shift with no discrepancies. Mix all drinks based on serving size as outline by company to keep costs down. Developed an organized and efficient work pace that keeps the customers at the bar and in the dinning room satisfied at all times.

-Achievements: Consistently scored 100% secret shopper reports.

Education

West Coast University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2018 - 2020)

Golden West College

Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2015 - 2017)